<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ACTDAILY</string>

    <string name="five_minute">5-Minute Shower</string>
    <string name="bring_bag">Bring Own Bag</string>
    <string name="drive_less">Drive Less</string>
    <string name="lights_off">Lights Off</string>
    <string name="local_produce">Local Produce</string>
    <string name="meat_free">Meat Free Meals</string>
    <string name="recycle">Recycle</string>
    <string name="refill_reuse">Refill and Reuse</string>
    <string name="unplug">Unplug</string>
    <string name="zero_waste">Zero Waste</string>

    <!-- activity_start.xml -->
    <string name="current_score">Your current score is:</string>
    <string name="register_button">Register your actions</string>
    <string name="information_textview">Man-made climate change poses the biggest threat to our existence.
        It is in everyone’s interest that we act now individually on a individual level to ensure a sustainable future. This application
        includes ten daily actions that would collectively have a good impact on the climate. Press “ACT” and collect points for each action
        that you have completed. If you have any questions,press the info button in the top right corner. </string>
    <string name="information_title">Information</string>
    <string name="act_climate_change">Act against climate change</string>

    <!-- activity_register -->
    <string name="register_your_actions">Register your actions</string>

    <!-- Descriptions -->
    <string name="five_minute_description">A normal shower gets rid of about 12 liters of water per minute. On average, a person
        shower for 13 minutes. Thus, get rid of 156 liters per shower. By going down to 5 minutes of showers, the average person
        will save 96 liters of water for each shower. In addition to the water savings, we also save energy used to pump and heat
        the water.</string>

    <string name="bring_bag_description">Plastic bags don’t biodegrade, they photodegrade. Which means that they break down into
        smaller and smaller bits. Moreover, a plastic bag can take up to 400 to 1000 years to break down. During that time, plastic
        particles contaminate the soil and waterways and are accidentally ingested by animals. On average, each human consumes 200
        plastic bags each year and 90% of them are only used once. Register your ACT each day that you have brought your own bag
        rather than buying one and using it once. </string>

    <string name="drive_less_description">Transportations accounts for one third of all CO2 emissions. 72% of that third is from road
        transport. For each time that you take an alternative means of transport rather than what you would usually do you can register
        that ACT.</string>

    <string name="lights_off_description">Production of electricity brings large environmental impacts – The combustion of fossil fuels, nuclear
        waste and more. The consumption of electricity has more than tripled since the 1970’s and increased with 14% since the year 2000. For
        each day that you have turned off all the lights that you are not in your current state needed for, register an ACT. </string>

    <string name="buy_locally_description">A lot of products, especially food and vegetables have transported a long way to reach your nearest
        grocery store. In addition, some may be frozen or chilled (impacting the climate even more). To not impact this chain of transportation,
        we encourage you to buy locally produced products and goods. Each time you buy locally, you can register your ACT. </string>

    <string name="meatless_meals_description">According to the World’s Wildlife Fund (WWF), beef accounts for 28 kilo CO2 equivalents per kilo food,
        shrimps 11, pork 4,8 and chicken 2,6. To have a positive affect on climate change, you should change your diet to be meatless. For each day
        that you do not consume meat, you can register your ACT.</string>

    <string name="recycle_description">By recycling you reduce the climate impact because the recycled goods is recovered and do not cause unnecessary
        CO2 emissions. When you recycle, you can register your ACT.</string>

    <string name="refill_reuse_description">One way to reduce unnecessary waste and production is to having your own reusable and refillable water bottle
        and coffee cup. By going a day without using a disposable bottle or cup, you can register your ACT. </string>

    <string name="unplug_description">Many devices consume more or the same amount of electricity in standby than in use. To effectively decrease your
        consumption of, you should unplug all devices that are not in use. By doing so for one day, you can register your ACT.</string>

    <string name="zero_waste_description">Clothes demands large resources to produce. They go through numerous of production steps and countries before
        being completed. It takes a lot of chemicals, water and energy to fibers. Moreover, on average, a third of all clothes bought never gets used and
        we throw away eight kilos worth of clothes each year. For each day passed without buying any unnecessary clothing you can register your ACT. </string>


    <!-- Notification strings -->

    <string name="main_notification_channel_name">Primary</string>
    <string name="notification_reminder_title">Don\'t Forget to Register your ACTs</string>
    <string name="notification_reminder_body">ACTs on climate change can\'t wait! Register and collect your points.</string>






</resources>
